<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Set-up on Advanced R Markdown Workshop</title>
    <link>/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Set-up on Advanced R Markdown Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra</title>
      <link>/docs/extra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/extra/</guid>
      <description>You’ll get the most from it if you enjoy learning how R Markdown works under the hood (which will involve reading some source code), and are seriously interested in hacking (playing) with:
 HTML, JavaScript, CSS, LaTeX, and command-line tools.  We will give minimal tutorials on these languages and tools in the workshop, but it may be easier for you to keep pace with the instructor if you already know them before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-requisites</title>
      <link>/docs/pre-requisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/pre-requisites/</guid>
      <description>You should take this workshop if you have experience programming in R and want to learn how to take advantage of the amazing breadth and depth of R Markdown. In this workshop, we will assume that you are familiar with the following:
Markdown  For example, do you know how to make first, second, and third-level headings using Markdown? Do you know how to use markdown to create links or make bulleted/numbered lists?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading</title>
      <link>/docs/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/reading/</guid>
      <description>This is a two-day hands-on workshop primarily based on the book &amp;ldquo;R Markdown: The Definitive Guide.&amp;rdquo; However, there are several other additional free and open source resources available
R Markdown: The Definitive Guide This book has been published by Chapman &amp;amp; Hall/CRC. The online version of this book is free to read here (thanks to Chapman &amp;amp; Hall/CRC), and licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Installations</title>
      <link>/docs/system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/system/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop, we will use R, RStudio, and a few R packages. RStudio is not required but recommended, because it makes it easier for an average user to work with R Markdown. If you do not have RStudio IDE installed, you will have to install Pandoc\index{Pandoc} (http://pandoc.org), otherwise there is no need to install Pandoc separately because RStudio has bundled it.
Install R and RStudio  The latest version of R (3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>